It was on this day in 2019 that my HBO comedy special, I Be Knowing, came out.
And a homie of mine sent me a text yesterday that I really, really appreciated because he
reminded me of this day because I guess Facebook reminded him. And he said, you know,
you've been doing this for 30 years at the top level and not many people can say that.
So I hope that you take today to give yourself some props. So I am giving myself some props
because folks tried to try me today and treat me like I'm some non-established folks, by the way,
where I'm just like, what are we talking about? And I feel like that text was so necessary because
it reminded me like they just posted a whole episode of my brother and me from 1995 on Instagram
the other day. Your girl was in there. You know, when I see y'all use the gifs from Insecure,
I'm always just like, oh, wow, because I'll be scrolling and there it is. And, you know,
my special came out in 2019 on HBO and HBO don't even exist anymore. So thank y'all for continuing
to support me on my journey. And yeah, your girl been here and I'm going further. And you can watch
my special on Max.